Okay, now let me get this straight.
They can't avenge them,
because they're arguing over
whether they're dead or altered?
Some things never change.
They always lose sight
of what's important,
so we're gonna do things our way.
If anyone interferes,
we'll take them down,
as simple as that.
[singer singing in English]
[explosion]
[narrator] Zazan has built her nest
in Meteor City.
[Bonolenov] Where's everyone else?
[Kalluto] That took longer than expected.
Nasty habit.
I really need to stop toying with my prey.
[laughs]
[laughing]
You're just no match for me.
Why don't you come back
when you've gotten your act together?
[Feitan] It looks like I'm out of shape.
But it's a good chance to practice.
[grunting]
[laughing]
[gasps]
I need to create an opening.
that girl somehow manages to make
that stupid vacuum appear out of nowhere.
Hmm, and I can't seem to catch her
with my gossamer.
This girl is surprisingly good,
but I cannot allow her
to escape my clutches.
I really hate to do this.
It's so hard on my butt.
But I have no choice!
[Pike] Love Shower!
[Shizuku] Whoa.
He might have me this time.
[Pike laughs]
With all the silk I keep spinning,
you've got nowhere to run to now.
Lucky me.
[laughs] Gotcha!
Even Bihorn couldn't snap my silk
when he tried,
and he's the strongest
out of all of us, no question.
Now, then, time to hand you
over to Mistress Zazan.
You took your clothes off.
I get it.
She widened an opening in my web
to slip through while protecting her skin.
With her power, it's certainly feasible.
[Shizuku grunts]
[Pike] She left her vacuum in the web,
[Shizuku] Maybe not,
but I could say the same thing to you.
I've been able to learn
the range and speed of your silk.
I won't mention that his anus
twitches twice before he fires.
I'll just keep my distance from now on,
so Blinky and I get the win.
[Pike] Win? [laughs]
I said that I'm going
to be keeping my distance,
not that I'm gonna run away.
Hmm?
Hold on a sec.
I'll show you the difference.
-Ready, Blinky?
-Gyo gyo.
Suck up every last drop of blood
from his body.
Gyo gyo!
[gasps] Hey.
Hold on a second. What?
Uh-oh. This is bad.
I'm getting dizzy.
I have to stop the bleeding.
[muffled] How's that?
Now you can't suck my blood…
[gasping]
[whimpering]
This is too much.
I can't cover them all at once.
Well, of course you can't.
I gave you exactly 29 bleeding wounds.
By my current calculations,
even accounting for the fact
you have eight limbs to work with,
it'll be impossible for you
to plug each laceration in time,
-unless you grow another limb.
-[groaning]
[Blinky turns off]
Mmm…
If you had wrapped it around yourself,
it would have stopped the bleeding,
wouldn't it?
Guess we're both pretty stupid, huh?
How can they move so fast?
[Phinks] Looks like
he's moving better now.
[Bonolenov] Still not
at the top of his game, though.
And how is he able to leap
from that position while attacking?
[gasps] Now he's over there.
They're on a completely different level.
[Shizuku] Whoa. Everyone's already here?
[Shalnark] His opponent's tough.
[Phinks] It's probably the queen.
[Zazan] Behind me?
Curse those worthless idiots.
Were they all defeated?
How dare you scar my beautiful face!
[panting] You're dead.
[gasps]
[growls]
[gasps] But her attack
didn't make contact.
No.
She threw some weak aura with that swing.
Feitan's idea to use Ko
just backfired on him.
He focused every last ounce of his energy
into a single point,
and it didn't do a damn thing,
and that error delayed his defense
by a split second.
She knows how to use her aura,
that's for sure.
Well, she isn't a queen for nothing,
you know.
[Zazan laughs] My body is indestructible.
Shouldn't we go help him?
Huh? Why would we?
That'd be me.
[Bonolenov] Wait.
We both arrived at the same time.
Oh, give me a break.
I was just waiting
until you finished your fight, you idiot.
[Kalluto] I was naive. I thought
I could rise to number two in no time.
But I'm utterly inferior.
It's hopeless.
Still, I can't give up.
I'll get my brother back,
no matter how long it takes.
[bone cracks]
There goes his left arm.
Hey, Feitan, you ready to tag out?
[speaking backwards] Piece of crap…
[Phinks and Shalnark gasp]
[speaking backwards]
You shouldn't press your luck!
We tried to watch him once before,
and we almost got killed.
His ability has a pretty wide range
that's activated by rage,
so he doesn't hold back.
I'm pretty sure
this one would obliterate you,
and probably instantly.
[Kalluto] "This one"?
There are different kinds?
Damn it! I wanna see.
[speaking backwards]
I'll pay back the pain.
With scorching heat.
Pain Packer!
Huh?
[Kalluto panting]
[screams]
You can run away, you know…
[Feitan continues laughing maniacally]
[laughter fades]
Out of gas already?
And the heat really wasn't that bad.
How unfortunate.
If only you had dealt me more damage,
you'd have had a quicker death.
Would you look at that?
It doesn't seem like any of them reverted
back to normal once their queen died.
[Chimera Ant groaning]
[straining]
[stammering] Kill me.
Kill us.
[scoffs] Hell no.
I don't do mercy killings.
But feel free to attack us.
Where's your pride?
You're still natives of Meteor City,
aren't you?
What's the matter with you?
Show us you got some fight left!
Okay, but we're not leaving, right?
We really don't have anything else to do.
If any more of those Ants show up here,
I'll crush them.
Killing survivors like that
left an awful aftertaste.
-[cell phone rings]
-Is it the boss?
No, Nobunaga.
He's asking if we'll go over
and help him with his job.
He's gotta be joking.
No chance in hell! Idiot!
Ah, man. This sucks.
-Say that again, and you're dead!
-[Feitan laughs]
[Shalnark] Hey! Be careful.
We're injured, you know?
[narrator] The Phantom Troupe
has successfully saved Meteor City
from the Chimera Ant invasion.
Meanwhile…
Gon and Killua are making preparations to
infiltrate the Republic Of East Gorteau.
The selection of citizens
to be presented to the King,
carried out by his own Royal Guards…
will begin in nine days.
[closing theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]